yes.
はい
Oh, it's been a while.
おー、久々
It's been impossible for a long time.
久々無理です
Long time no see.
久々
The atmosphere has changed, quite a bit.
なんか雰囲気変わったね、ずいぶん
I changed it.
変えました
Something has changed a lot.
なんか、めっちゃ変わった
Do you feel more like an adult?
なんか大人っぽい感じになった?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
I see.
そっか
Yes, did the move go smoothly?
はい、引っ越しは無事に終わったの?
The move was safe.
引っ越しは無事
Good.
良かったー
It was good, it was good.
良かった良かった
Is that so?
そうかそうか
what happened?
どうしたの?
I contacted you out of the blue today.
今日なんかいきなり連絡してきたけど
I need some money today.
今日なんかお金必要になっちゃって
Furniture, etc.
家具とか
I have finished moving.
引っ越しは終わったけど
It's finished, but I still have to buy furniture and a TV.
終わったけど、家具とか テレビとか買わなきゃいけなくて
I needed money.
お金必要になっちゃって
I told you to contact me.
連絡してって言ってたから
That's what it feels like.
そういう感じね
It's totally fine.
全然良いよ
The atmosphere has changed and it's really cute.
雰囲気変わったし、なんかめっちゃ可愛いじゃん
It's good, it's good.
良いじゃん良いじゃん
Good, not at all.
良いよ全然
I'm actually glad you contacted me.
むしろ連絡してくれて良かった
what?
何?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
Something like this.
こういうの
I really like it.
めっちゃ好き
Hey, did you get a boyfriend?
ねえ、彼氏でもできたの?
I haven't been able to do it.
できてない
It's getting hard.
硬くなって
It will become.
なるって
Are you proactive?
積極的だっけ?
yes.
はい
The T-shirt is also a nuisance, so take it off.
Tシャツも邪魔だから、脱いちゃって
Punky was really embarrassed earlier.
さっきパンキーめっちゃ恥ずかしいんだけど
It's really hard.
めっちゃ硬い
That's right, that's true.
なるよ、そりゃ
I'm the only one naked.
俺だけはだかい
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
It's getting really tough.
めっちゃたなってる
what?
何?
That's amazing.
すごいね
No, these aren't pants.
違う、これパンツじゃない
Not pants.
パンツじゃない
You're really handy with your feet.
めっちゃ器用だね、足
Super dexterous.
超器用
It's dangerous to stand like this while being fucked with your feet.
足でされてこんな立ってるのヤバいね
That's a pervert.
変態だね
It turns out to be a pervert.
変 態になっちゃうんだもんだって
He's really good with his feet.
足めっちゃ器用じゃ
yeah.
ん
Ah, you like Taka better, right?
あ たかのほうが好きでしょ?
Come to this side and take your time.
こっち側に来て、じっくりしながら
My sister says it's dangerous.
姉ちゃんヤバいって言っちゃうよ
I'm leaving.
出ちゃうって
Just my daughter.
俺の娘さして
Hey.
ねえ
You're trying to make the most of your life, right?
思いっきり生かそうとしてるでしょ、
now.
今
My sister is really wet.
姉ちゃんめっちゃ濡れてるね
There's so much going on, but why?
なんかめっちゃ溢れてるけど、どうして
Isn't it weaker in the front, not here?
ここじゃなくて手前弱くない?
As it is
そのま
Well, before I get down on my knees.
ま 膝つける前に
I can do it before I take a break.
休む前にやれるから
Wasn't it a bit more wet than last time?
濡れ方前回よりなんかちょっと すごくなかったですか?
what happened?
どうしたの?
The number of people who have sex has increased, right?
エ チする人間増えたでしょ?
for now
と り あ え ず
Well, today, I'll give you the home appliance stand.
じゃあ 今日さ、 家電台渡すからさ
Don't want to get off?
降りたくない?
From home appliances.
家電から